If you like this video, please subscribe to our channel.
Hello!
Yes, I would like to answer my 100 questions then!
My name is Lucky Fujitani.
I am from Yamagata Prefecture, and my member color is light blue.
Rainbow!
My nickname is Lucky Fujitani, which is my real name.
My birthday is yesterday.
What are you doing on the day the world ends?
I'm going to end the world.
What would you like for yakitori?
I order yakitori with cartilage.
Yakitori with sauce? Or salt?
Definitely sesame. I prefer salt.
Do you get white streaks in mandarin oranges?
The oranges I eat do not have white streaks.
Do you take white streaks out of yakitori?
My favorite hairstyle is a Mohawk.
I like spicy food. I like spicy food.
What color would you dye your hair?
As you can see, it's all blue.
Do you believe in psychics?
I don't believe in ghosts.
Who is your personal best dining companion?
My mom.
Mama Miya.
Do you have silky teeth? Momey teeth?
I don't know the difference.
Silk tooth
Can you eat a bowl of ramen noodles with any teeth?
Well, I had 60 the other day.
What do you believe in when you go on an expedition?
Dreams and hopes.
Which instrument would you play in a band?
Tambourine.
Would you peel and eat a baked sweet potato?
Would you peel a baked sweet potato and eat it?Do you peel the skin off a baked potato and eat it?
I don't.
What's the last dream you had?
When I wake up in the morning.
I was sleeping like this, and when I woke up in the morning.
I woke up in the morning and there was a monkey and a pheasant beside me.
They said, "Let's go fight!
I was Momotaro.
That's a lie.
What is your favorite season?
My favorite season is...
The season of my birthday.
But the pollen count is so high that my nose is runny.
It's perky right now.
Rice or bread? Bread?
Definitely rice!
Rice, rice, rice, rice, rice!
What flavor of ramen do you prefer?
Pork bone and soy sauce for sure!
Where would you prefer to get free transportation in the future?
Wow, absolutely free transportation!
Because if you make it, where would you go on a trip and where would you go on a trip and where would you go on a trip and where would you go on a trip and where would you go on a trip?
The process of going on a trip is fun, but it's no fun if you don't know where to make things!
What is your favorite sushi?
Rice with egg
I've never had it.
It's delicious.
If you could figure it out, what would you do?
Uh... a corrective corrective instrument.
If you could figure out the name of the group, what would it be?
Uh, we're not all in the same group.
What's your favorite word?
That's funny.
Where would you like to go on a trip in Japan?
LA.
Where would you like to go on an international trip?Where would you like to go on an overseas trip?
Kyoto.
What do you do on your day off?
Talking alone with imaginary friends.
How many meals a day?
One meal a day.
No way.
Ew! Ew!
What are you gonna do? Here.
Ew! Ew! Ew!
What's your favorite animal?
My favorite animal is...
My least favorite animal is rats.
Humans.
Dogs?
Cats?
Pheasant?
What are your favorite lyrics and songs?
What are your favorite lyrics and favorite songs?
What's your favorite song by Equal Love?
Um... A song about you and me.
What is your favorite English word?
Exciting
Do you have a driver's license?
I think I have a driver's license at this time, but I don't have it now.
I definitely have it at this time.
I hope, hope, hope.
How many seconds of weightless hitting?
One second!
Mach mach mach.
What is your favorite subject?
Japanese.
Are you shy?
Yes!
What's your favorite thing to do?
Spanking horses.To spank a horse.
Bye bye!
If I were to compare myself with one kanji character
It's "yin" in "yin qi.
Give me the highest and lowest voice you can.
Everyone, please don't take off your earphones.
And please be careful with your earphones.
Aaaaahhh!
And...
Wooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo
Oh, bang bang, a new face.
Yes, sir.
Habit?
Habit of moving my heart.
I really need to fix that.
What is your favorite TOW-OFF song?
Feeling.
Feeling, feeling, feeling.
What do you think about during a live performance?
What are you thinking about during the show?
Yes, I am.
Where I want to live in the future.
Which song is the most fun to sing live?
That one.
Um, Hotei's Bamminna.
What's your favorite ingredient in a hot pot?
Well, that's a tough one.
Um, a shoehorn.
Actually, Chinese cabbage. What's your favorite oden ingredient?
Um, toothpaste. Daikon radish, actually.
Who do you admire? Karon.
If you could take one thing with you to a deserted island, what would it be?
I wonder.
Mosquitoes.
If you could take a head of cattle, who would it be?
Who would you take?
Uh, Kaaya.Eh, Kaya.
I feel like it's going to be anyhow.
If Kaaya was here.
Who would you switch with?
Kaaya or Aya.
Sounds like a fun life.
If you were a man, who would you want to date?
Wow! I'm so confused!
Ew! I'm lost!
I'm lost.
Ehhhh...
but I had already made up my mind.
People are scary, aren't they?
This is Louie.
What sport would you like to do?
The sports I would like to try are
Foot-joints.
Running
What would make you the best male singer in the world?
The best singer in the world.
I don't want either one.
I don't want to be the best at either
I want to be the best MC in the world
Which would you rather be the tallest you want to be or not gain weight your whole life?
Well, I'd rather not get fat for the rest of my life!
Yes, I'm Princess Peach
What would you like to say to the newbies?
What song would you recommend to a complete novice?
Well, you must be a complete nerd.
What time do you go to bed and wake up?
Let's see, I go to bed at 4 a.m. and wake up at 4 a.m.
Zero minutes! Zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero.
Clothes to sleep in? Pajamas?
Suit.
If you lived in the country, would you live in the country?
Definitely the countryside!
Definitely the countryside!Absolutely rural!
A garden!
Countryside!
If you were to change the member colors, what would they be?
I'd like rainbow.
What's the most expensive purchase you've ever made?
What was it?
Souvenirs from the last tour in Hokkaido.
14,500 yen.
Yay!
What was your scariest experience?
I'd like you to put this in the summary section.
Well, I was in a haunted place with a group of people.
We were in a haunted place, and we heard voices.
This is for real, this is for real.
Then I started to get a little bit psychic.
I could tell if they were here or there.
I can tell if they are here or there.
Now I'm here and here.
What's your favorite onigiri ingredient?
Kelp!
What would you like to do in show business?
That would be... well, that would be... Princess Peach.
Mamamiya.
Models, do you pick the seeds out of the watermelon first?
No, I don't. I drink it all.
Then the watermelon grows back.
Per.
Is there anything you believed when you were little that you don't believe now?
I thought idols didn't really laugh, but they really did.
How many questions are you on now?
Hinamon! Hinamon, cute Hinamon.
Please keep Hinamon out.
Chuchu chuchu.
Here's another Hinamon.
Scary, scary, scaryScary, scary, scary.
Bye-bye, everyone! I'll catch up with you later.
What were you like when you were little?
I was rather cheerful.
My kindergarten teacher told me I was full of laughter.
How about now? I don't know. I don't know.
Are you a water person? Tea?
Water.
If you could produce a song for Mr. Far, what kind of song would it be?
Uhhhhh...
Woooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo!
I'd like to make a very strange song.
Teeth fell out, grew in, fell around, threw, or some other random thing....
What's today's side dish?
I want to make a strange song like "Today's side dish is an egg.
Do you have a karaoke box?
I don't go to karaoke, but I sing Furusato.
What do you do on New Year's Eve?
Shamisol!
Please give me a screentime.
There you go. I'm good at this.
May I? Gentlemen. Here we are.
Okay, everybody.
Here we go.
Okay, we're done.
This is something, isn't it?
Something like this.
What do you do on the road?
I can't sleep on the move, so I'm just moving around.
I'm just...
What do you always order when you watch a movie?
Popcorn.
I'm a voracious eater.
L of popcorn, L of drinks, a chicken and Naturals.
Yay.
Yuck.Yay.
Yes, ma'am.
What clubs were you in?
Crafts club.
What's the hardest song you've ever played in a talk show?
Yikes!
With Ivy!
Oh, Seamony.
How did you get into show business?
I used to love reading a magazine called Nikofuchi,
I had a crush on Kaon from the same agency. I still admire her.
I still admire her,
I always wanted to be in the entertainment industry,
I did all kinds of things, but..,
I couldn't make it,
I even tried to become a solo horse, and did many other things,
I found out that there was an audition, and I read about it on the page of Kaon's
I found out that there was an audition, and I read about it on the page. Nikofuchi's page.
And I thought, "What? I thought it was in Sendai,
I took it,
Here I am!
Yay!
Boom!
Do you believe in fate? I do! I believe in fate! I want to bump into him over that loaf of bread!
Where is he? Bread! Bread man!
Who's your favorite YouTube star? I want to brag about this. I like youtube a lot, I've been watching youtube since I was in elementary school.
I've been watching youtube since I was in elementary school, and even now, my favorite youtuber is Hajime Shacho, but I also like HIKAKIN, too.
I'm not a fan. I'm not a fan, I'm a child. I also like Hajime Shacho, and there are many others. There are a lot of them.
There are a lot of them. I like them a lot. I should probably say this.
I'm going to say a lot of things. I like Sushi Ramen Riku-san.
I also like that Katsu-san a lot. I like it more when I'm alone.
I like men who are alone.
Ha!
What were you into when you were little?
Um...
Let's see...Let's see.
Well, yeah, I guess.
Let's see...
Wow!
I wonder.
When I was little, I was addicted to...
Ochazuke.
Tell me what you're into.
Hatena
Tell me.
A very dark place.
The lighting.
What are your hobbies?
Editing videos.
Do you confess? Wait for it?
What?
Get in between confessions.
Wait a minute! You say, "Wait a minute!
Wait a minute!
I want to say it. I want to hurry up and confess to someone.
Are you a good swimmer?
I'm very good at it.
I can go to the end of the ocean.
Where would you like to go with the British Legion?
Hell.
Do you prefer Japanese food or Western food? Western food?
Japanese food.
If you could only eat the same thing for the rest of your life, what would it be?
Yaki soba (fried noodles)
But... but...
Potato soup made by my mom
What venues would you like to perform at?
There are so many!
Yokohama Arena
And a venue in my hometown
If I were to compare myself to an animal, I would say
I am weak and bitter
If you were to compare each member to an animal...
Rung-chan is a rabbit, right? If she wasn't a rabbit, I'd be pissed.
Rinne is a black cat
Yuna is a
is a can-gal that flies like a rocket.
Rinwoka is a...
Cheetah
Shinji is a
Squirrel
Karen is an ostrich
Ostrich
Mon-chan is a
Polar bear.
I'm a peacock.
Kaja is a...
A leopard.
A carrion.
In a word, what is your selling point, Tork?
What's your selling point?
First of all, he sells the Tohoku region.
And as you can see from this hundred qualities
I think what the nine of you are saying is totally different. I don't know anything about them.
I don't know what it is, but that's what I'm talking about.
They are all very kind.
Any singers you'd like to talk to?
Yes, I would.
Fluffy.
I love you, Fluffy.
Fluffy, I love Fluffy.
I forgot to say you're a YouTuber.
I'm Fuwachan, I love Fuwachan!
The part-time job I'd like to do is...
That one where you're rebelling the whole time.
I want to do it all the time!I want to do it all the time.
I want to do the same thing all the time.
My favorite snacks are
〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜 and
Potato chips.
What I like about you guys is...
The fact that you like me like this.
What do you want me to fix?
I'm getting so excited that I can't see my surroundings.
Hmmm...
Sorry.
What's one word of love for everyone?
Wow!
As Mr. Towel, my ultimate goal is
All of you.
Every last one of you.
All of us.
We're going to the ends of the earth.
We'll drive them to hell
Ue.
Finally, a word of love to the members of Tohoku-san.
Such a funny, funny, funny child who came from such a funny, funny, funny place,
Thank you for always taking good care of her.
Thank you for always taking care of her.
Please take care of Pichanko from now on.
Thank you very much.
And thank you also for watching this video.
I know you will be young by now, but I hope you are not just a kid.